Previously on Pretty Little Liars....
What happened in the woods?
Toby Cavanaugh is dead.
Somebody killed him. I saw his body.
Ahh! Oh, God.
Maggie, I am so sorry.
Did pastor Ted hire somebody
to work on the church?
Hannah: I put a five dollar bill
in the church collection box,
it had some dice drawn on it.
And later that day, Caleb's dad had it.
Do you really think he
would steal from the place
that just hired him?
There was some trouble with the old badges.
People getting in? People getting out?
Ezra Fitz has applied
as a substitute teacher.
I have to ask, are you seeing Ezra Fitz?
No, I'm not.
All I want from you and
your mother is that car.
Look at all that's happened
since you turned me down
on our little drive up the mountain.
But I believe in second
chances. You need me.
(Door buzzing)
You have visitors.
Spencer?
I'll be in the hall if you need me.
Emily: Hey. You knew we were coming, right?
We spoke with your mom. We
wanted to be here the first day.
But she said you were going
to be home tomorrow, so...
She still believes that?
She thinks that I'll be able
to sleep through the night
if I just take a nice bubble
bath and lay in my own bed?
- I think what she wants is...
- I know what she wants, but
they don't make a loofa that
scrapes out the inside of your head.
The park rangers found a body.
Emily and Aria: Hannah! What?
The sooner she knows, the sooner
she checks out of this place.
What Hannah is trying to
say is we have good news.
They found a body in the woods.
The police believe it was a camper.
It was Toby.
No, Spence, it wasn't.
This person, he'd been missing for awhile
and he was nowhere near
where you thought you saw...
I know what I saw.
It was Toby.
Hey, so, um, I was thinking tomorrow night
when you get home, we could all...
I need to stay here. I need more time.
Time for what?
Hannah.
Shuffling around in Mona's old slippers
isn't going to get her any better.
Hannah, chill.
You know what...
I would not dine here, if I were you,
I had to sneak around in that kitchen,
and I saw a roach big
enough to wear an apron.
Moving. On.
You are not crazy. This place is.
I'm too tired to have
this fight right now, guys.
I feel safe here.
Those bars don't just
keep you from getting out,
they keep other people from getting in.
(Knocking on door) Uh, need a minute.
Your friends are leaving.
Do you want to say good-bye?
I already did.
♪ got a secret, can you keep it ♪
♪ swear this one you'll save ♪
♪ better lock it in your pocket ♪
♪ taking this one to the grave ♪
♪ if I show you then I'll know you ♪
♪ won't tell what I said ♪
♪ 'cause two can keep a secret ♪
♪ if one of them is dead ♪
Sync by chamallow
Corrections by wilson0804
www.Addic7ed.com
Hannah: Have you seen my make-up bag?
(Sighs) No, but I think everything
that was in it is on my pillow.
Okay, don't start. I only slept for,
like, 20 minutes.
Emily: Why do you keep looking out there?
Because Wilden knows I'm staying here.
That's what you're thinking about?
I'm having dreams about our
friend having her head shaved,
and you're looking...
I have lots of other
things that are keeping me
up at night, okay Emily?
If that car I dunked suddenly
learns how to float, then...
If Wilden's looking for his car,
then he's not "A."
Okay, besides cars
don't float, if they did,
pilgrims could have driven here.
Why is there a wet towel on my bed?
(Knock on door)
Pam: Ladies, you better get hopping,
or you're not going to
have time for breakfast.
Hannah: Oh, none for me, thanks.
You know I love her, but
somebody's got to teach
that girl the word "fold."
It was a rough night.
Honey, look. I know it's
hard seeing a friend suffer,
but if the doctors think she...
Doctors aren't helping Spencer.
Okay, she still believes that was Toby.
Well, you can't get caught
up in that kind of thinking.
Don't take on a tragedy that
has nothing to do with you.
Mom! Okay, you work at the precinct,
can you at least tell me when
you know more about the body?
(Sighs) Look,
if it'll help you move on from this,
then yes.
You'll know when I know.
Sure if this is big enough to split?
I think that we should go sit inside.
We could also eat this in my car
and duck every time somebody walks by.
If I'm telling the principal
that we're not involved,
I don't think we should be seen splitting
- a cruller on the sidewalk.
- All right,
we're not going backwards.
We'll figure it out.
Look...
Nothing between us needs to change.
(Phone ringing)
It's Maggie.
Hey, what's up?
What time?
Tomorrow... um, no, I just have a...
You know what, yeah. I can pick him up.
Yep.
What's going on?
Malcolm's karate class
gets out at the same time
as my second interview.
Well, I'd offer to help, I just figured
after the whole
falling-off-the-bed incident...
Well, you know I don't blame you for that.
It's not about me.
- So, Maggie blames me.
- You know what,
honestly, I would love it
if you picked up Malcolm.
If I put off this interview,
someone else is going to get that job.
(Laughs)
Well, what are you going to tell Maggie?
I can deal with her.
And what's even trippier
is we both have scars
below our left knee.
And, you know, granted,
my dad got his in prison, but...
That was a joke.
(Laughs)
Mmm, what's that smell? New perfume?
No, it's air freshener.
Emily's mom sprayed it all
over my clothes and then,
when I wasn't looking,
she sprayed it in my hair.
Ask her to spritz you tonight.
My dad wants to take us to a nice dinner.
Caleb, he does not have to do that.
Stop.
Look, not only are you the person that
brought him back into my life,
but you're the reason
he gets to stay in it.
And you got the man work.
Let him get you an entrée.
Can't you just ask your mom for
a copy of the coroner's report?
Aria, the report doesn't say not Toby,
it says John Doe.
It's not going to change Spencer's mind.
(Phone rings)
Who's that?
Um, Shana.
Why does she keep texting you
while Paige is out of town?
Is she into you?
Sorry you guys, Caleb had a lot to share.
Why are you blushing?
Why is she blushing?
Shana's cruising her, and I
think that she should shut it down
before it turns into ex and the city.
Guys, I'm not thinking about Shana.
We need to help Spencer.
No, Em, you saw her face.
She's not getting out of
there unless we kidnap her.
Or we actually take the body there
and prove to her it isn't Toby.
Em, that's not a real option.
No, but, taking a picture of it is.
And we've been to that morgue before,
what's stopping us from going back?
Um, do we really have to answer that?
Eddie: Ever played this one?
Um, no. Looks like it's
a bit before my time.
So is Duke Ellington.
If he walks in the door,
are you going to ask him
not to play the piano?
Wren: Spencer? I just
learned you're admitted.
I didn't know.
Eddie, uh, could you check on Mr. Paterson?
He may need assistance
getting to physical therapy.
He had it this morning.
Then, perhaps you could do a follow-up,
check on his pain management.
How're you feeling?
Um...
Spencer, if there's anything
I said or did that...
No, you're not the reason that I'm here.
Who chose this game? You or Eddie?
Eddie. Why?
He played it with Mona,
when she first arrived.
Yeah, she was a bit obsessed with it,
until she eventually traded it for cards.
(Phone ringing)
I'm afraid I've got to push on.
I'll check on you later.
Okay.
I'll see you later.
Hannah?
I've left your mom several
messages and I haven't heard back.
Is there a better way that I can reach her?
Uh, she's in New York right
now for a training seminar.
Why, what's wrong?
We just need her to weigh
in on a delicate issue.
Who's we?
Mrs. Montgomery, what's going on?
(Sighs)
I'm on the church's restoration committee,
and something's come up.
Wait, is this about Caleb's dad?
(Sighs)
How well did your mom know
Jamie before she recommended him?
Look, I'm trying to help.
It's just, it's really
hard to defend the honor
of someone you don't even know.
I'm hoping it's all just
a big misunderstanding.
And what's the misunderstanding?
Jamie... removed the
bronze bell from the tower
to have it repaired, but the one that was
returned is evidently of much lesser value.
Wait, that's what this is about?
They miss their old, crusty bell?
To the tune of $8,000.
Please, don't say anything to Caleb,
just have your mom call me.
It's got great bones.
They built these churches to last.
When do they expect you to be done?
I'm going to take my time.
I want to get this right.
Oh, before I forget.
What is this?
It's for you.
Open it.
It's an angel.
It seemed appropriate.
I don't know what to say.
(Phone ringing)
Oh, I hate these damn things.
Let me turn this off.
Actually, it's Pastor Ted.
I may have to get this, excuse me.
Hello?
Veronica: I thought this
might make you feel better.
And then maybe on the
way home, we can stop...
- I'm not coming home.
- Just at least put on the blouse.
Mom, I told you I'm not ready.
Well, as soon as you're
in your own bedroom,
- surrounded by your...
- Look, mom,
I can't just go back
to dinners at the club.
You don't have to wear the
blazer, just put on the...
(Yelling) I said I'm not ready!
What happened between you and Toby?
I'm not moving from this spot
until I get a real answer.
The last time I saw someone in this state,
clinging to a secret
this hard, it was Alison.
A few weeks later she was dead.
(Door opens)
(Sighs) Alison.
Where were you? I thought you were
asleep in Spencer's room.
I had to go out.
For what?
What happened to your mouth? It's bleeding.
I must've scratched myself on a tree branch
on my way over to the house.
Can I go upstairs, please?
Why did you have to go to your
house at three in the morning?
Mrs. Hastings, please.
I can't talk about this.
Let me get some ice for
your mouth. Just stay there.
Please?
Here.
Did you have a fight with someone?
Mrs. Hastings, if you tell my parents,
it's only going to make it worse.
Promise me you won't say anything.
Come here.
Shh.
I'm just being weird.
Overly sensitive. I'm fine.
You never told this to the police?
Of course I did.
But I made up my own mind about
who went after her that night
and I kept that to myself.
Well, who?
Why? Mom, how could you not say anything?
Because if Jason went after us,
exposing your father as his, too,
it'd be my family breaking
down in the middle of the night.
So, you still believe Jason?
No, I don't. Not anymore.
But I'm starting to wonder about others.
I need to ask.
Is Toby not the person
that we thought he was?
Sorry, guys, I'm going
to have to hit the road.
There's a problem at
work I gotta deal with.
What, right now?
I've just been fired.
What... what are you talking about?
It seems the wrong bell
got hung up in the tower...
I'm gonna have to go down to the
foundry myself and clear this up.
Do you want me to come with you?
No, you guys finish your dinner,
I'll sort this out. I'll see you later.
(Door closing)
Okay, who am I supposed
to text if I see someone?
Me. Not Hannah.
We're using her phone to take the picture.
Hannah, pay attention.
What? I'm sorry.
My boyfriend's dad got nailed for stealing.
Where do you sell a hot bell, anyway?
Hannah, focus. I don't want to be
in there any longer than we have to.
We find John Doe, we take the
picture, and we get out of here.
If it's bronze, you
probably melt it down first.
Melt it into what?
Why are we still discussing bells?
Because Caleb thinks his dad is a Saint,
and I know he's selling
pieces of our church online.
Okay, forget it. I'll do this alone.
Hannah: How are we gonna
know which one is John Doe?
Emily: We have to go through those racks.
Um, no. You are going through those racks.
This isn't a clearance sale,
Emily, and I'm freaking out.
All we've done is walk through those doors.
It doesn't matter! I smell dead people.
Fine, just get your phone ready, okay?
I'll hold it, but you have to aim it.
I just want to close my eyes.
Hannah: God, this is so wrong.
You spend your whole life doing crunches,
getting rid of tan lines, not
eating that second pudding.
And then in the end you're
just a stale loaf of bread
lying on a rack.
Um, maybe you can help me with this loaf,
- I can't find the tag.
- Wait.
Em, what if it really is Toby in there?
It's not. And Spencer needs to know that.
Okay, but just in case
I don't know if I can
handle seeing his face.
So can we just look for
his tattoo or something?
It's not Toby.
(Cell phone beeps)
(Door closes)
(Elevator bell dings)
Emily: Ahh!
(Cell phone rings)
Em, someone's coming.
Come on, we have to go.
Em, come on!
(Knocking on door)
Hi, sunshine.
Hey.
Good book?
It's okay.
Can I ask you something?
That game that you
wanted to play yesterday?
I heard it was one of Mona's favorites.
Who played it with her?
I don't recall.
Mona liked to play a lot of games.
Yeah, but Wren...
Dr. Kingston, he said she was
"obsessed" with this one.
Well, he would know.
What is with you and him?
What do you mean?
Eddie, are you the
person behind the trouble
with the visitors' passes?
Did you let somebody in who...
It wasn't me.
Was it Dr. Kingston?
Take your pill.
You may be sleeping, but you don't look
like you're getting any rest.
I won't tell anybody.
Trust your instinct. Mine told me,
from the minute that guy got here,
it wasn't for the right reasons.
Let's just leave it at that, okay?
Hey.
Did you get my messages?
Yeah, I've been cramming for algebra.
I have a make-up test
in, like, ten minutes.
Well, my dad's screwed.
The foundry claims there is no mix-up,
and they have the paper trail to prove it.
Well, maybe if your father
spoke to the church committee,
and told them that... told them what?
Why should he have to
defend himself to a bunch of
small-minded people who
think someone is a thief
just because they don't
tuck in their shirt?
Did I press mute or something?
Why are you being so quiet?
I'm just listening.
You did a lot of that last night, too.
I don't know what to say, Caleb.
Since when? Hannah you
have an opinion about
everything, from honey boo-boo's hair cut
to the weird look the
lunch lady gave you when
you asked for butter on your corn.
Look, I just don't think that
your dad has changed as much
as much as you think he has.
Look, the night that he
got the job at the church,
I put money in the church collection box,
and when he paid for the
pizza, he used that same bill.
How could you possibly know that?
Because there was a pair
of lucky dice drawn on it.
It was the same bill, Caleb.
(School bell rings)
(Scattered chattering)
Hi. Excuse me, yeah, I'm
here to pick up Malcolm.
Oh, he was already picked
up about ten minutes ago.
He was? Oh, so Maggie must have...
Oh, no, his mom didn't
come today, it was a friend.
Uh, Aria Montgomery.
Something wrong?
No. No, everything's fine, thanks.
(Carnival music playing)
(Children laughing)
(Laughing)
Carnival barker: Knock
them down and win a prize!
(Carnival barker continues)
(Laughter)
Ella: Aria?
I didn't know you were coming here tonight.
Yeah, I'm came to meet
up with Ezra and Malcolm.
Are you all right?
Is Maggie here, too?
I don't know, maybe.
Honey, we talked about this.
And I know you want to make it work, but...
- Okay, mom, I can't do this right now.
- Aria!
You're going to be the one that gets hurt.
Not to mention a confused
little boy who's still wondering
how this stranger is suddenly his father.
He needs help working
through it, but not with you.
Malcolm already has
somebody looking out for him.
I have to go.
Be right back, I'm going to
drop this off to room 217.
What is that?
A book.
One of the patients was
asking for it earlier, so...
Yes, well, our patient needs her rest.
You can give it to Spencer tomorrow.
I'm off tomorrow.
All right, then I'll
give it to her for you.
We're not having the same
problem again, are we, Eddie?
(Fair music playing)
Have you heard anything yet?
Nope. (Phone rings)
For all I know, he's already skipped town.
Well, I spoke to my mom...
Hannah, it's not up to your mom
or you, or me to dig him out of this.
Is this everything?
Yeah, almost. Just to find my English book.
All right, I'll be out front.
(Door bell rings)
Jamie: Hey.
I was on my way to your place,
and I saw your car out front.
Where were you?
Oh, making phone calls... hey.
Was trying to track
down a guy who helped me
with the dry wall. And
see if he can help...
Help with what? Back up your story?
What's his cut?
What?
Caleb, don't do this right now.
Hey, you should listen to your girlfriend.
I am.
And I believe her when she
says this isn't the first time
that you've stolen from that church.
What are we talking about here?
We aren't talking. We are done.
Last night, you were my defender.
- What happened?
- I woke up,
and I realized that this isn't the
first time that you've screwed me over.
Oh, I see.
I'm still that person, huh?
Somehow you managed to
forgive your mother's sins.
Don't suppose it's got anything
to do with that fancy car
she tossed at you.
That has nothing to do with this.
Maybe not, but it's got to
be easier to point a finger
at someone with a rusty pick-up
and no permanent address.
Isn't that all the proof you needed?
All the proof that I needed
were the ratty hand-me-downs
that I had as a kid.
Remember the winter coat
that ended at my elbow?
And the unsigned permission slips?
And the social workers,
and the foster families
who slammed doors in my face when
they were tired of looking at me?
That is my proof!
Yeah.
Wow, when you put it that way...
I guess I wouldn't believe me, either.
Aria: Should I call the police?
Emily: Yes. Wait.
Unless you think it will make it worse.
What's worse? "A's" got Ezra's kid.
I'm just saying, you saw
them, Malcolm wasn't hurt.
But if you call the cops, "A" might...
Don't. Just don't.
Okay, I swear, if something
happens to that little boy
because of me, I don't
know what I'm going to do.
Aria. Walk over to the police station,
and report it. I'll meet you there in ten.
(Sighs)
Malcolm?
There's gonna be another
show. The man outside said so.
I'm early.
You know, I was supposed to pick
you up from your karate class, right?
But your friend picked me up instead.
She said her name was Alison.
Come on, we should go.
Your dad's probably wondering where we are.
(Phone ringing)
_
Emily?
Um, mom, I figured you'd be home by now.
I thought I was clear this morning.
Look, I know you want answers,
but you can't be doing this.
Go home. We'll talk about this later.
What's going on?
This is not the time.
Why are they making you stay late?
Emily, go.
I'll call you when I'm on my way.
One, two, three, four...
(Humming coming from the distance)
(Humming continues)
(Humming getting louder)
Didn't your mother have this?
Your mother.
Really, I must have left it at your house
and didn't get it back.
I left a lot of stuff there.
Is it just me, or was sixth
grade the best year ever?
I didn't even know you then.
Oh, honey,
you didn't even know me when you knew me.
(Music starts playing)
Come on, give it up, Spence.
Let's pretend that you're getting ready for
your first boy-girl dance party.
No one ever tells you that the practice
is so much more fun than the real thing.
Spencer: Was it Toby?
Was he the one that
gave you that bloody lip?
Toby?
Oh, sweetie,
girls fight much dirtier than boys.
I'm lucky she didn't leave a scar.
She? Who?
You stopped dancing.
I don't... I don't want to dance.
I'll change the song.
No, I can't. I haven't slept in three days.
Come on. I'm looking for something.
The star on Mona's game board.
Oh, that. It's in there.
♪
Wren: Spencer.
What are you doing?
♪
So...
You're Malcolm's new hero.
He had a blast tonight.
What did he say?
Ah, not much. Maggie said he
mumbled something about puppets,
and then fell right to sleep.
Huh.
Oh, she asked me to pass along her thanks.
You know, if you keep
spoiling him like this,
he's not going to want
to go with anyone else.
Ezra?
I don't think that I can do this anymore.
Aria, I was kidding. You won't have to.
No, I'm saying I don't think
that I can do this anymore.
What? What do you mean?
It isn't just the two of us now,
and eventually somebody's
going to wind up hurt.
And I'd rather it be me.
I just need to go home.
- Now? Okay, well then, just
let me get a waitress... - No.
You finish, I'm...
I'm going to walk. I think that
the air will be good for me.
Hey. I've had these days.
I promise you things will
look different in the morning.
Spencer: How many times did she visit her?
What is that?
Mona kept souvenirs.
How many times did Cece visit her?
- I wouldn't know.
- Yes, you would, Wren.
You authorized it.
And I was almost suspended for it.
Mona was under restriction
at that time, no visitors.
And you broke the rules for her because...?
Cece called me and was
desperate to see her.
She thought she could help her.
Help her with what?
Recover from the psychic
wounds inflicted by your
late friend, Alison.
You sure it wasn't the other way around?
Quite sure. Alison pulled
some stunt at a frat party
that got Cece kicked out of university.
Ali... got Cece kicked out of school?
Yeah, Cece came out the other side,
and she thought she could
serve as a role model for Mona.
And I agreed.
How did she even know
that Mona was even in here?
Melissa called her.
(Knock on door)
Emily? Is Hannah home?
No. She's out with Caleb, why?
Mom?
What's going on?
Why were you carrying
that missing persons file?
I promised I wouldn't
keep anything from you.
But I have to make sure that
you keep this from your friends.
Can I have your phone, please?
What?
This is very sensitive information,
- if it got out before the police...
- Mom.
Please, what is it?
They found another body early this evening.
A young man.
Late teens, early 20s.
No identification.
What are you saying?
It could be Toby?
I don't know.
How can they not know?
There was significant
trauma to the body, Emily.
It's gonna take some time
before they're certain.
We'll know more tomorrow morning.
Do you want to take a walk or something?
It was stupid.
You gave someone a second chance.
That's never stupid.
We talked about this road
trip we were gonna take.
Ride bikes, go out west.
(Sighing)
I was already mapping it out.
We can take a trip sometime.
- I know it's not the same,
but... - It would be better.
Because I'll be with someone
who I know is looking out for me.
I'll get us refills.
(Bell tolling)
(Phone ringing)
(Bell continues tolling)
So, basically "A" was framing
Jamie the whole time?
Do you think that bill from
the collection box was...
Don't you?
Caleb is never going to forgive me.
Where is he now?
He went to go find Jamie.
But even if he does, what
is he supposed to tell him?
He may just have to find a
way to tell him the truth.
Caleb's familiar with the workings of "A."
So is Ezra.
Do you plan on telling
him who bought his kid
a big, fat balloon today?
(Knock on door)
Aria: Em? It was the wrong body.
Hannah: What?
The John Doe, the one in the mask.
It was the wrong one.
Emily, you're not making sense.
They just found a body tonight.
In a shallow grave out in the woods.
Where?
Exactly where Spencer said it was.
They found her purse close by.
Mona's voice: Look at
all that's happened since
you turned me down on our
little drive up the mountain.
But I believe in second chances.
Spencer's voice: You don't
have to ask me again, Mona.
I'm in.
Sync by chamallow
Corrections by wilson0804
www.Addic7ed.com